(Penny:)Who's ready for another beer?
- I'm good.
- No, thank you.
(Penny:)Girls.
I am having the nicest time.
(Raj:)You guys are like family to me.
You know that, right?
(Leonard:)That's great. Get out.
- What? Why?
- Penny and I have some issues to talk about.
(Raj:)Oh, pish on your issues.
(Raj:)You guys are fine.
Yes, you've had some bumps
along the way.
(Raj:)I mean, Penny, you've always known
how this man has felt about you.
(Raj:)But you made him grovel for affection.
- Okay, hold on...
- Don't blame yourself.
He was a groveler from way back.
(Raj:)But the point is,
the two of you got past it.
And you go and propose to this poor girl
in the middle of sex?
(Raj:)That was some weak tea, dude.
(Leonard:)Some people might say it was romantic.
(Raj:)Yeah, no.
(Raj:)But yet, here you two are still together.
(Raj:)Even after you and I
had our crazy naked night.